const BasicQuestions = [
    {
      question: "What is the first letter of the English alphabet?",
      options: ["A", " B", "C", "D"],
      correct_option: "A"
    },
    {
      question: "Which letter comes after G in the alphabet?",
      options: ["F", "H", "I", "J"],
      correct_option: "H"
    },
    {
      question: "What letter is the 19th letter in the English alphabet?",
      options: ["R", "S", "T", "U"],
      correct_option: "T"
    },
    {
      question: "Which letter is a vowel?",
      options: ["B", "C ", "I", "F"],
      correct_option: "I"
    },
    {
      question: "What letter comes before K in the alphabet?",
      options: ["H", " I", "J", "L"],
      correct_option: "H"
    },
    {
      question: "What letter is often called a double-u?",
      options: ["W", "M ", "V", "X"],
      correct_option: "W"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not a consonant?",
      options: ["E", " S", "Q", "Z"],
      correct_option: "E"
    },
    {
      question: "What letter comes after P in the alphabet?",
      options: ["O", "Q ", "R", "S"],
      correct_option: "R"
    },
    {
      question: "Which letter is silent in the word knight?",
      options: ["K", "N ", "I", "G"],
      correct_option: "K"
    },
    {
      question: "What letter is often used to represent a heart shape?",
      options: ["V", " H", "Y", "X"],
      correct_option: "V"
    },
  ];
  
  export default BasicQuestions;
